<note>
	<title>Weekend with our Folks</title>
	<content><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE en-note SYSTEM "http://xml.evernote.com/pub/enml2.dtd">
<en-note><p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;">2012-07-09</p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"> </p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;">This past weekend we visited my family back home. The drive home went quick and we faced only small pockets of traffic. Thankfully I've done the trip several times and know all the fast tricks. We arrived around eight, and had a good tour and some wine before dinner. Mom prepared fajitas and different dips, all of which were delicious. The funniest part of dinner was Marcia spilling her wine. She was in rare form this week, spilling many things (eg. salsa) and making messes (eg. trash bag dripping), but it was all fun and harmless. We stayed up pretty late talking before retiring to bed, where I slept incredibly well!</p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);"><br clear="none"/></span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);">Saturday we had a big breakfast which my dad prepared. Then Emily, Dave, Dad and I went outside to shoot guns for a while. It was a lot of fun, and all of us hit a CD or two. I shot pretty well I think, though made a massive faux pas when I shot into the ground trying to disengage the hammer. Cut my hand up pretty bad, but thankfully I handled the gun safely. It was a good experience to share with everyone.</span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);"><br clear="none"/></span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);">In the afternoon I drove the Gawnes, Emily, and Mom to the Wintergreen winery, then up around the Parkway and back home. Some nice views, but it was still scorching hot as it had been all week. </span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);"><br clear="none"/></span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);">We left shortly after returning home so that we could get back in time for dinner and to receive Sarah from NYC. Dave and Marcia bought us steak and beer, and we had a great dinner. There had been a fair amount of talk about Sarah and Gor beforehand, and a small row happened after dinner. It turned out to be great for our relations, as Sarah, Emily, and Marcia all had a heart to heart about the situation. I pray God's Will be done in this whole messy situation. </span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);"><br clear="none"/></span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);">Dave and I, on the other hand, had a great time talking about older movies and watching It's A Mad Mad Mad Mad World. We had a few beers and laughed at all the great jokes of the movie.</span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);"><br clear="none"/></span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);">Sunday came too soon, and we took the folks to the airport. It was an odd day, and sad to see everyone go. Gor came over in the evening, after the girls and I had had a nice time at the pool. We ate Domino's pizza and hung out. We played Ticket to Ride, which I narrowly won in the end. The score wasn't even close, but I would have lost horribly if not for one connection between two cities to complete most of my destinations. </span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);"><br clear="none"/></span></p>
<p style="padding: 0px; margin: 0px;"><span style="background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0078125);">This week I learned a lot about grace and patience, and how fortunate I am to have joined this amazing family. No one is perfect, myself included, and yet we can all still have such great times together. I'd gladly welcome Dave and Marcia to stay with us another week!<br clear="none"/></span></p></en-note>]]></content>
	<created>20120709T205136Z</created>
	<updated>20120709T211343Z</updated>
	<tag>journal</tag>
	<note-attributes>
		<source>mobile.iphone</source>
	</note-attributes>
</note>